1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East Records 6347
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series III. Internal Documents, 1973-2011; 1950-2011
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 6, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Files related to the hearing against 1199 (with Popper part of rhe charging party).
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 7, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 10, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 11, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 12, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 13, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 14, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 15+16, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 17, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 18, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 19, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 24, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 25, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 26, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 27, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees AFL-CIO April 28, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Witness List, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    For 1984 hearings.
  - N.U. Hearing - Notes, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Charges/Hearing Rules, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - US District Court Southern District of NY, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Files related to an additional hearing. Popper is not named directly in this hearing.
  - USDOL, In the Matter of Spring, 1984 Election of Officers (Box 13, Folder 13-16)
  - Summary of National executive Board Hearing on Charge 4, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Agreement Between 1199 and League of Voluntary Hospitals, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Popper 1199 History Project, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Delegate Assembly Mtgs., 1984-1989 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Budget Schedules, 1984-2003 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - 1199 National Staff Meeting February, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Work Plan, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Organizing Directors Meetings, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Rochester Statistics, 1989-2009 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Directory of Local Unions affiliated with the Rochester Labor Council (4), 1990-1993 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Constitution and By-Laws - Rochester, NY, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Service Employees Pension Fund of Upstate NY, 1992-2006 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Grievance Appeals Committee, 1993-1999 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Labor and Healthcare Report, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Dues Payment Summary Sheet- Rochester, NUHHCE/SEIU, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
  - NYS Health Care Locals Mtg., 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Health Care Division Board Meeting, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 8-12)
  - SEIU - Health Care Division Board Meeting, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
  - 1199 - SEIU, 1997-2002 (Box 7, Folder 23-24)
    Includes handouts, home health aids, and speech notes.
  - SEIU Materials, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - SEIU - NY State, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 19-20)
  - Recommendations of the SEIU Task Force on Representation, 1998 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Staff Items, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - SEIU - Employee Manual, 1998-2005 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Health Care Employees Pension Fund: Agreement and Declaration of Trust, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1199 Upstate Officers, 1999-2018 (Box 10, Folder 15-16)
  - SEIU Materials, 1999-2015 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1199 Exec. Council, 1999-2019 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - SEIU - NYS Council, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Summary from the President's Committee, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - SEIU Resources/Surveys (Hart Research), 2000 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Constitution of 1199SEIU, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - 1199UP Sr. Op. Team, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 27-29)
  - (SEIU) 1199 Upstate, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Exec. Board Mtgs., 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 23-30)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - SEIU Materials, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Personal information (needs ot be removed), communications guidelines & budget, 1199SEIU newspaper too
  - 1199UP Financer, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 30-31)
  - 1199UP E-Board Items, 2001-2005 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 1199UP Sr. Ops. Meetings, 2001-2017 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
  - 1199UP Training Fund, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - SEIU - Board Meetings, 2002-2004 (Box 8, Folder 17-19)
  - 1199 Grievance Policies, 2003 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Meeting Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Rochester Member Issues, 2003-2011 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Training and Upgrading Fund, 2003-2017 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Directory of Local Unions affiliated with the Rochester and Genesee Valley Area Labor Federation (6), 2004-2005; 2008-2009; 2012-2013; 2014-2015; 2015-2016; 2017-2018 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Benefit and Pension Fund Joint Session, 2006-06 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Union Trustee Training, 2006-06-01 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Proposed Amendments to 1199SEIU East Constitution, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Constitution of 1199SEIU East, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - SEIU Healthcare, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Includes notes from healthcare conference.
  - 2007 Rochester Union Elections (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Work Plan, 2007-2008 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Recurring Solidarity Expenses, 2007-2011 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - 1199 Upstate NY, 2008-2010 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Pension Plan and Memorandum, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1199 Upstate NY Officers, 2009-2011 (Box 10, Folder 6-8)
  - Executive Director's Annual Joint Report, 2009-2010 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    2009 through First Quarter 2010.
  - Annual Delegates Awards Dinner Program, 2012 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - SEIU Healthcare Benefits, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Includes information about Obamacare
  - 1199 SEIU - United Healthcare Workers East, 2013 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
    Niagara Falls Memorial Hospital
  - WNY Hospital Team Mtgs., 2013 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - AFL-CIO Annual Meeting/Forms, 2013 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Western NY ALF - Annual 2013 Meeting (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - AFL-CIO Agendas/Documents, 2013-2015 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Proposal for Associate Member Status, 2013-2018 (Box 34, Folder 41-42)
  - SEIU Staff Retreat, 2015 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1199 SEIU Elections, 2016-2019 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Unity and Power, 2017 (Box 7, Folder 17-18)
  - 1199 Joint Officers, 2017 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - 1199 NYS Council, 2019 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - CBTU Annual Awards Dinner, 2019 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Resolution of the Board of Trustees, 2004-06-11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees: Training and Upgrading Fund, 2004-12-02 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2005-04-11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2006-03-21-2007-03-21 (Box 1, Folder 13-15)
  - Annual Meeting of the National Benefit Fund and Employee Pension Fund, 2006-06-23 (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
  - Joint Session of the National Benefit and Pension Funds, 2006-12-14 (Box 1, Folder 8-10)
  - Meeting of the Boards of Trustees, 2006-12-15 (Box 1, Folder 11-12)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2007-12-13 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2008-07-16 (Box 1, Folder 17-19)
  - Joint Session of the Board of Trustees, 2008-07-17 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Joint Session of the Board of Trustees, 2008-07-18 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2008-12-11 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Joint Budget Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2008-12-11 (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2010-07-21 (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
  - Joint Budget Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2010-12-16 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 2011-07-11 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - 1199, Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 1199 Health and Safety Project, Undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - 1199 National Benefit Fund for Hospital and Health Care Employees, Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 1199 Training and Upgrading Fund, Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - AFL-CIO Posters/Resources, Undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Blanks Forms and Surveys, Undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - By-Laws of 1199SEIU Rochester, Undated (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - District 1199-Rochester Union Office Support Staff Duties, Undated (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Fact Sheet on Founding of Union, Undated (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Notebook, Undated (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Rub Sheet - AFL CIO National Organizing Coordinating Committee, Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Statistical and Tactical Information Report, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Strategy and Research Checklist, Undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - V.O.I.C.E of 1199 Program, Undated (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Volunteer Organizing Committee, Undated (Box 34, Folder 47)
- Series IV. Campaigns and Organizations, 1969-2020; 1948-2020
  Includes all documents on the individual locations of the union, movements and strikes that they have taken part of, and their community and political involvement. Organized chronologically.
  - Retail Drugstore Employees - Local 1199 Split from RWDSU, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Campus Times, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - UR Journal, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Journal - U of R News Magazine, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Campus Times, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - University of Rochester Notes, 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Campus Times, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Campus Times, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Campus Times, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - UR Journal, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - UR Journal, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - UR Cinema Group, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Campus Times, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Campus Times, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Campus Times, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Campus Times, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - UR Journal, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Campus Times, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - UR Journal, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - University of Rochester: Schedule of Classes, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Campus Times, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Campus Times, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Jack Kemp, 1972-1982 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Hospital Agreement, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    Strong Memorial Hospital/University of Rochester
  - Graduate Employee Org. - University of Michigan, 1974-1977 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Agreement between Strong Memorial Hospital and National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees (10 agreements), 1974-1976; 1976-1978; 1978-1980; 1980-1982; 1982-1984; 1984-1986; 1986-1988; 1988-1990; 1990-1992; 1992-1994 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Agreements with League of Voluntary Hospitals and Homes of New York, 1974-1976, 11/1/01-4/30/05, 6/1/04-4/30/08 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Labor Rally - April 26, 1975 Washington, D.C. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital Negotiations, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Lakeshore Nursing News Clips, 1975-1982 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital News Clippings, 1975-1992 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Agreement between the University of Rochester, Univ. of Rochester, River Campus and SEIU (11), 1975-1977; 1977-1978; 1978-1980; 1980-1982; 1982-1984; 1984-1986; 1986-1988; 1988-1990; 1990-1992; 1992-1994; 2010-2012 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - University of Rochester - Campus Times Clippings, 1975-2012 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital Negotiations, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Workers World Party, Center for United Labor Action (CULA) Youth Against War & Fascism (YANF), 1976-1981 (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Fred Eckert NYS Senate, 1976-1986 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Agreement between Lakeshore Nursing Home and National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Anthony l. Jordan News Clippings, 1977-2018 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital Negotiations, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - People's Power Coalition, 1978-1981 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Wilson Memorial and Ideal Hospitals Decuments, 1978-1981 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - ACTWU Local #3-T, 1978-1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Lakeshore Nursing Documents, 1978-1983 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Union Social Events, 1978-2017 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Jacob Javitts, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - F. Glenn King, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital NLRB Unit Determination Hearing, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Environmentalists for full employment, 1979-1981 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases From Politicians, 1979-1982 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement between Lakeshore Nursing Home and 1199 Rochester, 1979-1984 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    2 agreements - (Nov. 1979 to Jan. 1981) and (Feb. 1983 to Feb. 1984)
  - Anthony L. Jordan Health Center, 1979-2005 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Monroe County Human Relations Commission, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital Negotiations, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Elm Manor and Wedgewood Ownership Transfer, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Bread & Roses Project -- Rochester, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Campaign for Lower Energy Prices Citizen/Labor Energy, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Coalition for Justice in the Federal Budget, 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Robert Abrams, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Barber Conable - U.S. Congress, 1980-1982 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Action for a Better Community (ABC), 1980-1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Metro-Act of Rochester, 1980-1985 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Continuing Developmental Services Documents, 1980-1988 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - 1199SEIU Political Endorsements, 1980-1988 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Rochester & Vicinity Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1980-2001 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Anthony L. Jordan Health Center, 1980-2019 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Vote to Affiliate with SEIU, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Solidarity Day Demo Sept. 19, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Industrial Management Council of Rochester, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Thompkins County Hospital Contact Lists, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Common Cause, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Rochester Area Workers Compensation Council, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - David Gantt, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - John Erb, 1981-1988 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Agreement between Anthony L. Jordan Health Center and District 1199 - Rochester… (6 agreements), Jan. 1981 to Dec. 1982; Jan. 1983 to Dec. 1984 2 copies; Jan. 1985 to Dec. 1986; Jan. 1989 to Dec. 1990; Jan. 1991 to Dec. 1992; Jan. 1993 to Dec. 1994 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Finger Lakes Health Systems Agency, 1981-2003 (Box 27, Folder 51)
  - Rochester Area Hospitals Corporation (RAHC), 1981-2019 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Labor Action Coalition of New York, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - WNY Labor Coalitions for Jobs, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Gray Panther, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Health Association of Rochester, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - June 12 Rally for Nuclear Disarmament June 12, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Bill Benet, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Alfonse D'Amato, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital CBA, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Mario Cuomo, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Unemployed Workers Council, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - John LaFalce, 1982-1986 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Strong Memorial Hospital Univ. of Rochester Medical Center, 1982-1990 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - 1199 Split from RWDSU, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Meetings on Political Topics, 1983-2018 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Walter Mondale, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - New York City 1199 Hospital Strike, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Finger Lakes Health Systems Agency, 1984-1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Peace & Justice Education Center - Rochester, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Mark Green, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Volunteers of America - Documents and Clippings, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Labor Day Celebrations, 1985-2014 (Box 33, Folder 80)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital Negotiations, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Agreement between Volunteers of America Adult Care Facility and 1199…, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - IBP Dakota City Worker Struggle, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Anthony L. Jordan Medicap Dispute, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Documents Outlining Vote Between SEIU and AFSCME, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - News Clippings on SEIU/AFSCME Vote, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Jesse Jackson Campaign Documents, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 81)
  - Comparisons Between AFSCME and SEIU, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Mtg. Notices Concerning Merger Vote, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Endorsements in Support of SEIU, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Magazines in Support of SEIU, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Posters and Fliers in Support of SEIU, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Other Handouts in Support of SEIU, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Magazines and Videos in Support of AFSCME, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Articles and Letters in Support of AFSCME, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Posters and Fliers in Support of AFSCME, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Agreement between Continuing Developmental Services, Inc. and 1199 (3 agreements), Mar. 1988 to Mar. 1990; Apr. 1990 to Apr. 1992; Apr. 1992 to Apr. 1994 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Agreements with Continuing Developmental Services, Inc., 3/12/88-3/31/90 and 4/9/94-4/12/96 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Affiliation Proposals of AFSCME and SEIU, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Charges Against AFSCME Supporters and Posters, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - University of Rochester NLRB Decisions, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Rochester Labor Council, AFL-CIO, 1989-2014 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Letter on the Frey Campaign, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 82)
  - Agreement with DePaul Adult Care Communities, 1994-07-01-1996-12-31 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Visiting Nurse Service/UR Medicine Home Care, 1994-2018 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital "Patient Centered Care", 1995 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - University of Rochester/Strong Memorial Hospital Negotiations, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Local 144 - SEIU, 1996-1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - AFL-CIO Materials, 1996-2002 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Perrin Interviews with Strong Memorial Hospital/1199 Workers, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - 1199/SEIU Partnership, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Mostly political/legislative agendas
  - MLK Day Celebrations and Demonstrations, 1997-2023 (Box 33, Folder 83)
  - Nortonian Nursing Home Documents, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Dennis Rivera Press Conference, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    On the Pataki Medicaid cuts (99')
  - Partnership and Unification Agreements (1199Upstate), 1999 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Drafts of 1199Upstate merger Agreement, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Constitution of Local 1199Upstate, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Negotiation for 1199Upstate Merger, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Staff Meetings About 1199Upstate Merger, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Contextual Documents for 1199Upstate Merger, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Supporting Documents for 1199Upstate Merger, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Agreement with Corning Hospital, 2000-11-30-2003-06-30 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Agreements with Kaleida Health, 2000-12-01-2005-05-31 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Agreements with Strong Memorial Hospital, 2000-2012 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Rochester Health Commission, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - St. Luke Health Services News Clippings, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Children's Hospital of Buffalo - Union Literature, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - NY Union: Child Care Coalition, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Mercy Rehab Strike (Auburn), 2002 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Children's Hospital of Buffalo, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - SEIU 2002 Strike (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Merger Between 1199Upstate and 1199SEIU, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Movement to Save Buffalo Children's Hospital, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - News Coverage of Buffalo Children's Hospital, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 46-48)
  - Agreements with Strong Memorial Hospital, 2002-2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Agreements with Greater New York Health Care Facilities, 2002-10-01-2008-04-30 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Agreements with Jennifer Matthews Nursing and Rehabilitation Center, 2002-2008 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Organizing Rochester, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Contains documents relating to specific locations and general organizing
  - Rochester-Genesee Valley Area Labor Federation (RGVALF) Annual Conference, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Labor Programs in Buffalo - Computers & Unions, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Internal Communications From Corning Hospital Strike, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Press Releases About Corning Hospital Strike, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - Letters to the Editor About Corning Hospital Strike, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - News Coverage of Corning Hospital Strike, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 43-45)
  - Episcopal Church Home Documents, 2003-2004 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - Rochester-Genesee Valley Area Labor Federation Annual Conference, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - RLC Sequicentennial History Project, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Agreements with GMR Living Centers, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Agreements with Wesley Gardens Nursing Home, 2004-2008 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Agreement with Niagara Falls Memorial Medical Center, 2005-04-21-2008-04-21 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Agreement with Brooks Memorial Hospital, 2005-05-01-2008-04-30 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Agreement with Brylin Hospitals, 2005-06-30-2008-07-01 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Agreement with Lockport Memorial Hospital, 2005-09-18-2008-03-31 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Metro Justice of Rochester, Inc., 2005-2017 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - UPSEU Materials, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists Annual Conference, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Agreement with Sheehan Memorial Hospital, 2006-01-01-2008-04-30 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Agreements with Blossom Health Care Center, 2006-05-01-2008-04-30 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Agreement with Mount St. Mary's Hospital, 2006-08-18 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Agreement with Bertrand Chaffee Hospital and Jennie B. Richmond Home, 2006-09-13-2009-09-12 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Agreements with VNA Home Care Services, 2006-12-01-2008-05-31 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Agreement with Sodexho at Sisters of Charity Hospital, 2007-07-16-2010-07-16 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Election Agenda/Forms, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Eastman Dental Center, 2007 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Rural-Metro Ambulance Corporation, 2007-2013 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Agreement with Kaleida Health, 2008-06-01-2011-05-31 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Coalition for Economic Justice, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - WHEC-TV/AFTRA-TV Dispute, 2009-2010 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - 1199SEIU Community Allies, 2009-2016 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Home Health Aides Initiative, 2009-2018 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - March on D.C., 2010 (Box 7, Folder 25-28)
  - RLC Tax Forms, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Letters About RWDSU Mott's Strike, 2010 (Box 21, Folder 49)